[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone. <br /><br />Click \"Continue\" when you're ready to move on.","rt":58694,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":218604,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6< /sub>, y ou start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":10783,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":229388,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":2151,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":231540,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5 "],"rt":6351,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":237891,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1119,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":239011,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":10208,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":249220,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":951,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":250172,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":4319,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":254491,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2 because 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":1271,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":255763,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum  is 6 or  bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":3795,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":259559,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":815,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":260375,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":7319,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":267694,"internal_chunk_id":"0 -0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":1095,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":268790,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":2759,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":271550,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":991,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":272542,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, t o perfor m +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":2465,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":275007,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1007,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":276015,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":2711,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":278727,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":3559,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":282287,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":2463,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":284750,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1183,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":285934,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":17575,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":303510,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the thing that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Sim ilarly,  3 is its own inverse under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":32465,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":335976,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":10519,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":346496,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1199,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":347696,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of  an elem ent is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":1951,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":349648,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":983,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":350632,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":2712,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":353344,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Corr ect! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1104,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":354448,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":1968,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":356416,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":760,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":357176,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /> <br /> ( Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":7832,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":365008,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":4936,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":369944,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simply be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":13563,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":383507,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":" We have  one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because of this, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":18384,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":401891,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can  make ev ery other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":7655,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":409546,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":14047,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":423594,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","response_history":["Yes","No"],"rt":6087,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":429682,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry,  that's  incorrect. 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":12153,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":441836,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":2583,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":444420,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 4 is not a generator under  +<sub>6 </sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":12183,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":456604,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":3335,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":459940,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":2399,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":462340,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions abou t a new  operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedback to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":9328,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":471668,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":5751,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":477420,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":1032,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":478452,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0. 11-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":3648,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":482100,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":2984,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":485084,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":4903,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":489988,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":2319,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":492308,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":2728,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":495036,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"5, because 4+1 equals five, and this is less than 9, so  you don't have to do anything else to it. ","response_history":["5, because 4=","5, because 4+1 equals five, and this is less than 9 a","5, because 4+1 equals five, and this is less than 9 ","5, because 4+1 equals five, and this is less than 9, so  you don't have to do anything else to it. "],"rt":26651,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":521687,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"3, because 8+4 is 12, and because that is 9 or higher, you have to subtract 9 from it. 12-9=3","response_history":["3, because 8+4 is 12, and because that is 9 or higher, you have to subtract 9 from i","3, because 8+4 is 12, and because that is 9 or higher, you have to subtract 9 from it. 12-9=3"],"rt":27230,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":548918,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0, I believe 0 is the identity under +9 because it still works in the same way that +6 does. Anything added to it will become itself. ","response_history":["0,  I blie","0, I bli","0, I bl","0, I believe 0 is the identity under 9 be","0, I believe 0 is the identity under 9 b","0, I believe 0 is the identity under 9 ","0, I believe 0 is the identity under 9","0, I believe 0 is the identity under +9 because it still work sin th","0, I believe 0 is the identity under +9 because it still work sin t","0, I believe 0 is the identity under +9 because it still work sin ","0, I believe 0 is the identity under +9 because it still work sin","0, I believe 0 is the identity under +9 because it still work si","0, I believe 0 is the identity under +9 because it still work s","0, I believe 0 is the identity under +9 because it still work ","0, I believe 0 is the identity under +9 because it still works in the same way that +6 does. Anything added to it will beca","0, I believe 0 is the identity under +9 because it still works in the same way that +6 does. Anything added to it will become itself. "],"rt":42490,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":591409,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":10620,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":602032,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","response_history":["7"],"rt":2087,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":604120,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"6, because the inverse just means the other number it would take in order to add up to 9. 6+3=9, so 6 is the inverse of 3. ","response_history":["6, beca use the inverse just means that ","6, because the inverse just means that","6, because the inverse just means tha","6, because the inverse just means the other number it would take in order to add u ","6, because the inverse just means the other number it would take in order to add up to 9. 6=","6, because the inverse just means the other number it would take in order to add up to 9. 6+9=","6, because the inverse just means the other number it would take in order to add up to 9. 6+9","6, because the inverse just means the other number it would take in order to add up to 9. 6+3=9, so the ","6, because the inverse just means the other number it would take in order to add up to 9. 6+3=9, so the","6, because the inverse just means the other number it would take in order to add up to 9. 6+3=9, so th","6, because the inverse just means the other number it would take in order to add up to 9. 6+3=9, so t","6, because the inverse just means the other number it would take in order to  add up t o 9. 6+3=9, so s","6, because the inverse just means the other number it would take in order to add up to 9. 6+3=9, so 6 is the inverse of 3. "],"rt":44355,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":648475,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no, because 2 can't make 1,3,4,5,6,7,8 by itself under +9","response_history":["yes, because 2=","yes, because 2+","no, because 2 plus its","no, because 2 plus it","no, because 2 plus i","no, because 2 plus ","no, because 2 plus","no, because 2 plu","no, because 2 pl","no, because 2 p","no, because 2 can't make anything ","no, because 2 can't make anything","no, because 2 can't make anythin","no, because 2 can't make anythi","no, because 2 can't make anyth","no, because 2 can't make anyt","no, because 2 can't make any","no, becau se 2 can 't make an","no, because 2 can't make a","no, because 2 can't make 1,3,4,5,6,7,8 by itself in ","no, because 2 can't make 1,3,4,5,6,7,8 by itself in","no, because 2 can't make 1,3,4,5,6,7,8 by itself i","no, because 2 can't make 1,3,4,5,6,7,8 by itself under =","no, because 2 can't make 1,3,4,5,6,7,8 by itself under +9"],"rt":56545,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":705020,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"yes, because 3+3 can equal 6 and that would remain 6 under +9","response_history":["yes, because 3=","yes, because 3+3 can ea","yes, because 3+3 can equal 6 and that would remain its","yes, because 3+3 can equal 6 and that would remain it ","yes, because 3+3 can equal 6 and that would remain it","yes, because 3+3 can equal 6 and that would remain i","yes,  because  3+3 can equal 6 and that would remain 6 under ","yes, because 3+3 can equal 6 and that would remain 6 under =","yes, because 3+3 can equal 6 and that would remain 6 under +9"],"rt":30439,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":735460,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no, because it can't produce 1,2,3,4,6,7,8 by itself under +9","response_history":["no, because it can't produce 1,2,3,4,6,7,8 bys","no, because it can't produce 1,2,3,4,6,7,8 by itself une","no, because it can't produce 1,2,3,4,6,7,8 by itself under _","no, because it can't produce 1,2,3,4,6,7,8 by itself under =(","no, because it can't produce 1,2,3,4,6,7,8 by itself under =","no, because it can't produce 1,2,3,4,6,7,8 by itself under =9","no, because it can't produce 1,2,3,4,6,7,8 by itself unde r =","no , because it can't produce 1,2,3,4,6,7,8 by itself under +9"],"rt":40130,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":775591,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"yes, because 6+3 is 0 under +9, because 6+3=9 and you must subtract 9 from it, making 0.","response_history":["yes, because 6=","yes, because 6+3 is 9 u","yes, because 6+3 is 9 ","yes, because 6+3 is 9","yes, because 6+3 is 0 under +9, because 6=3","yes, because 6+3 is 0 under +9, because 6=","yes, because 6+3 is 0 under +9, because 6+3=9 and you must subtract 9 from it ","yes, because 6+3 is 0 under +9, because 6+3=9 and you must subtract 9 from it, making 1","yes, because 6+3 is 0 under +9, because 6+3=9 and you must subtract 9 from it, making 0; ","yes, because 6+3 is 0 under +9, because 6+3=9 and you must s ubtract  9 from it, making 0;","yes, because 6+3 is 0 under +9, because 6+3=9 and you must subtract 9 from it, making 0."],"rt":46603,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":822194,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use \"+_n\", and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":7934,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":830129,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"(inverse of 1) + (+n) 1 = n","response_history":["inverse of 1)",")inverse of 1)","inverse of 1)","(inverse of  1) =","( inverse of 1) + (+n)1","(inverse of 1) + (+n) 1 = n"],"rt":60417,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":890547,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"(inverse of x) + (+n) X = n. The inverse of a number (X) is just whatever number plus X that it would take to get to n. ","response_history":["(inverse of x) =","(inverse of x) + X","(inverse of x) + (+n) X -","(inverse of x) + (+n) X = n. The inverse of a number (X) is just whatever number plus X that it would take to get to n. "],"rt":75002,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":965550,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub >n</sub>  without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I don't think it is possible to know if element x is a generator under +n without seeing whether it can make all the elements. ","response_history":["I don't think it is possible to know if element x is a generator uner ","I don't think it is possible to know if element x is a generator uner","I don't think it is possible to know if element x is a generator une","I don't think it is possible to know if element x is a generator under +n without seeing whether it can make all the elemtne","I don't think it is possible to know if element x is a generator under +n without seeing whether it can make all the elemtn","I don't think it is possible to know if element x is a generator under +n without seeing whether it can make all the elemte","I don't think it is possible to know if element x is a generator under +n without seeing whether it can make  all the  elemt","I don't think it is possible to know if element x is a generator under +n without seeing whether it can make all the elements. "],"rt":42561,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":1008111,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":11712,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":1019823,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","response_history":["False","True"],"rt":8799,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":1028624,"internal_chunk_id":" 0-0.13-0 "},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must divide n.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","response_history":["True"],"rt":9690,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":1038314,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words why your answer is corret.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"True","response":"If x isn't a generator under +n, it must be a multiple of a divisor of n because that is the only way it wouldn't be able to make the other numbers","response_history":["if ","if","i","If x can be a","If x can be ","If x c","If x is a multi","If x is","If x isn't a generator under +n, it mi","If x isn't a generator under +n, it must be a multiple of a divisor of n because ","If x is n't a ge nerator under +n, it must be a multiple of a divisor of n because that is the only way it wouldn't be able to make the other numbers"],"rt":54615,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":1092929,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Sometimes","response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":48207,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":1141139,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words why your answer is corret.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"sometimes","response":"If this  is the  case, it is sometimes a generator under +n because it just depends on what the number is","response_history":["If this is the s","If this is the case, it is sometimes a generator under +n because it just depends on what the number is"],"rt":35288,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":1176431,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Sometimes","response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":21716,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":1198150,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press \"Continue\" to continue.","rt":1615,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":1199766,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"23","response_history":["23"],"rt":1576,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":1201342,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"Bachelors Degree","response_history":["Bachelors Degree"],"rt":2367,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":1203710,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please  list the m.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"College algebra and statistics","response_history":["College algep","College algebra and statistics"],"rt":9783,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":1213494,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"3 - seen it used or explained","response_history":["1 - never heard of it","3 - seen it used or explained"],"rt":6363,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":1219857,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi ","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"3 - seen it used or explained","response_history":["3 - seen it used or explained"],"rt":2375,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":1222233,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":3575,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":1225809,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":2536,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":1228345,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"3 - definitely","response_history":["3 - definitely"],"rt":2063,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":1230409,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Female","response_history":["Female"],"rt":1896,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":1232305,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English","response_history":["English"],"rt":3623,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":1235928,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":2856,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":1238785,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"","response_history":[],"rt":1895,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":1240681,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"}]